# **Deovrat Singh**

## Technology Analyst

Skilled UX/UI Designer, seeking to use proven skills in UX/UI designing, wireframing and prototyping to enhance user experience in your esteemed company.

My 3+ years of career graph reflects my proficiency in my work. I am continuously learning, open to be versatile to learn new technologies and to optimize my skills and capabilities to face any challenging opportunity offered by Organization.

## **Personal Info**

#### **Address**

Flat No.5, GH39, MDC 5, Panchkula

#### Phone

7307043856

#### F-mail

deovrat.singh619@hotmail.com

#### Date of birth

1992-06-15

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/deovratsingh-8abb69102/

## Skills

Adobe Experience Design



Skilled

**UXPin** and



Wireframing. Prototyping

Skilled

Adobe Photoshop



Adobe Illustrator



Communication

Skills

Advanced

## Languages

**English** Hindi



Punjabi

## **Experience**

2015-06 -**System Engineer Trainee** 

2015-11 Infosys Ltd.

Trained in Python, SQL, Java and passed with proficiency.

2015-11 -**System Engineer** 

2016-11 Infosys Ltd.

- Creating New User Types and their configurations in cloud
- Changing UI of desktop and Mobility screen of Cloud
- Enhancing new design changes on the cloud

2016-11 -Senior System Engineer

Infosys Ltd.

2018-07

- -Deployed new plugins integrating with the cloud .
- Worked on the front end of the plugin designs i.e HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Defect solutions on the design and working of plugins.

2018-08 -**Technology Analyst** Infosys Ltd.

present

- Worked closely with Design, Development, Program Management, Marketing Research, Analytics and other teams to develop user-centered features

- Monitor work against the production schedule, provide updates to the Design and Development Manager and report any technical difficulties
- Collaborate with developers, product managers, QA and marketing to create amazing user interfaces

## Education

2007-05 -Alok Senior Secondary School, Udaipur

2010-05

Under CBSE Board - XII - 84 % , Year -2010 - X - 86 %, Year - 2008

2011-07 -

**SRM University NCR Campus** 

2015-05 Passed with 8.1 CGPA

## Certificates

2018-03 Become a UX designer from Scratch by Interaction-Design.org

Google Digital Garage 2017-03

Interests

Photography

Photoshop Manipulation and Retouching

Travelling